not fair you three have been playing for  hours  when is it going to be my turn  shut up sonia video games is a man's  hobby go play with your dumb barbies  yeah i get lost or better yet make like  a woman and go fetch me and bros a  couple of some dr peppers  god damn it she's crying again bro go  hit her  [Music]  what the hell mom  turn the tv back on you old hag we're in  the middle of a game here  shut it you've been holed up in this  house all week you smell like uncle  chuck's beer farts it's time for a break  don't you give me that look greeny you  won't die by being away from the xbox  for a few hours if anything you might  finally grow a pair of balls  oh yeah we got this in the mail this  morning too  open it [ __ ] do my bidding  would you lookie there the oracle of  delphius sent you a birthday card why  don't you kids go over there and wish  him a happy birthday but mom the last  time we saw him he pulled down his pants  and chased sonic around the backyard in  broad daylight  that's right and isn't he on the sex  offenders registry  of crying out loud stop with the excuse  it's not like he actually caught you  only because bart levy was there to piss  down his throat  look he knows rape is illegal now so he  probably won't do it again and besides  he's getting up in years and i'm sure he  would value the company especially from  his three favorite hedgehog lips be sure  to wear the tight underwear today bro if  you do it will be harder for the oracle  to get to your swinging hairy ball sack  mom can i borrow your phone to play  roblox they wouldn't let me join in  yeah sure give me like three minutes i  wanna play now  [Music]  [Music]  well whip my ass with a yowie paddle and  call me sonic are the celestial buddies  above deceiving me  i know i sent out an invitation but i  still didn't expect anyone to show up  and so many of you too come and come and  we're in the middle of a party  huh  is that captain squeeze  oh yes  he's my um room eight we've been getting  along very well as of late  it's good to know he found a friend huh  boys  or cool work a lime out of microwave  aquitos  be a nice little mate and whip me up  another batch before i [ __ ] in this  chair just to spite you  [Music]  [Music]  hey oracle i got this shirt and cost 55  million dollars that was marked down to  three bucks because nobody was rich  enough to buy it but me  is there anywhere i can hit my mark down  shrimp in peace without the smell of the  crusty [ __ ] stained carpet wafting in my  face with every bite  you can't ride the balcony outside but  we share it with our neighbors  i'm not sure if they're outside right  now though  i'll take my chances you enjoy the party  tubby  excuse me is this seat taken  huh oh no no it's not  well up shrimp pretty fancy are you guys  having a party  not really i mean the others are i guess  but i'm just having my lunch  so i take it you're from the apartment  next door  huh um yeah i am  my name is austin i'm an ocean wildlife  researcher who advocates for the safety  of sea creatures so i don't eat fish or  shrimp okay  i have a trillion dollars  hey oracle you got any baby wipes in  this place  why is that dear boy  no reason  haha i get it you spilled something  didn't you  i sure spilled something all right  you should be able to find some in the  bathroom down the hall and to the left  try not to open any other doors in the  house all right their broom closets and  their stuff to the brim i'm afraid  everything may come tumbling out if you  did  wait did he say left or right  all hell like it even matters  this wouldn't be the first time i  dropped a fat poop in the closet  manic don't be deceived by what you see  what the hell was that  that couldn't have been real could it  my mind must be playing tricks on me  yeah that's it he just got out of jail  so it's illegal for him to break the law  now  hey manic haha this is going to be a  silly question  but you didn't open any door besides  this one especially on the right did you  no no of course not oracle i did exactly  as you instructed me too  i see that's nice to hear because if you  did  i think you and i are going to have a  little problem if you're catching what  i'm throwing  [ __ ]  i hear you  golly you're not going to leave without  washing your stinky hands are you  come over here and use the sink by the  door and wash those smelly hands  give me that ass  oh my god  [Music]  i don't get it what sort of person buys  82 chili dogs in a single afternoon  it's not within our job description as  door dashers to judge someone by the  contents of their order  yeah yeah i know do you think he's a fat  goal that would be funny  god he is fat you're not planning on  eating all of these yourself are you fat  boy  of course not i'm going to share them  with my friends what kind of fatty do  you take me for  the total will be 164 dollars and 22  cents  pay up  so what's with the costumes are you  going to a bondage convention  these are not costumes these are  standard issue your tactical uniforms  don't mind her she's sort of a stuck up  [ __ ] i'm 9s  you're hell member number two type e in  your presence what was that  i said you're high number number two  type b  look can we speed things up here i've  had a pretty long week  what is that oh that  that's just a pickup truck  no that is a machine and i [ __ ] hate  machines  9s stop it it's not going to kill you  stand back 2p i'm going to try hacking  it  [Music]  [Applause]  it's not working is it possible that  it's attempting to add me back  too [ __ ] look there's smoke coming out  of the upstairs window i think someone  is in trouble  bro are you okay  we saw smoke  thank goodness you found me bro the  oracle  someone plucked me in here and wants me  dead someone  what do you mean my own little baby bro  bro there's something you must see  follow me into the basement and all will  make sense  let's go to be  something tells me they're going to need  our aid in combat  here's a better idea you're going to  shut your mouth and we're going back to  the holiday inn where you're going to  make me a ham and cheese sandwich and  then i go to bed  it's not fair why do you always treat me  like i'm a sex object  well duh why do you think you wear such  tight shorts  oh god oracle oracle lift your head  or a call of delphias hang on i'll get  you out of those chains in a jiffy  oh sonic what a pleasure to see your  sparkling face after so long  i must ask  what year is it  it's 20 22.  i see then i've been locked in here for  30 minutes  oracle what are you hiding from us  weren't we just throwing a party  together with all your friends  i see so you met him  my evil clone  evil clone like zach bell's brother  xenobel  it all started a week ago where i shoved  a magical crystal ball up my fat ass for  no particular reason  so don't ask it accidentally cast a  spell  the spell you see was a duplication  spell  after i realized that i had cloned  myself  i told him quickly that he would have to  go back into the crystal ball or else i  would hit him  but he didn't want to mostly because it  had been between my butt crack  i did the one thing i shouldn't have and  showed pity to him because he was  handsome like me  so i made him an offer that if he  cleaned up around the house and did the  dishes  basically be my [ __ ] he could stay as a  servant but over time he became  jealous  jealous  jealous of what i had and he wanted a  piece of it  he stole it all from me my food my life  my dreams  sonic manic i ask you please please put  an end to him  he's sapping away my life energy if you  don't kill him in 10 minutes i will fade  away and [ __ ]  looks like we have another job to do  it's quite a shame we don't have our  medallions on us  ha got you covered on that one bro  it's a good thing we ran out of toilet  paper yesterday  ah you thought you could fool us  imposter you're going down harder than  the sonic underground tv show by geek  entertainment  [Music]  watch yourselves he has access to all of  my magic  i fear sonic the hedgehog is in danger  did i say you could talk [ __ ] put those  cute boys eyes to good use and pedal  there i smell chili dogs  [Music]  to be nines you're here  how did you know we were in trouble  because i called them  you did you really saved our bacon for  the 26  448th time  alas it's time for you to return home my  friend  get in my balls  no i refuse to go back in there  i'd rather die than face another second  in your rancid [ __ ]  what are you doing sonic  take the shot already  i i can't what do you mean you can't  i don't know who the real one is  just shoot them both he's a pedophile  anyway  shoot him he's the fake one  no he is  don't listen to his lies sweet boy  don't let him play you for a [ __ ]  you're smarter than that  kill him now before i rape you myself  fat boy  oh i just don't know what to do  you need not worry yourself too much  [ __ ] i bought lovely modern color of  raised in shall save the day as usual  what's that  this manic is a legendary artifact that  has been passed down in the montclair  family for generations  it's called the golden pepto detector of  dresden it can detect anyone within a  10-foot radius unless you know if any of  those people are on the sex offender  registry  warning warning  danger pedophile detected hide your kids  not a pedophile  the one on the left is a fraud get him  [Music]  [Music]  haha who would have thought  maybe in some cases being a pedophile  isn't so bad after all  uh-huh i wouldn't go that far beach  i would  well i wouldn't  [Music]  [Music]  when the lights go  [Music]  [Music]  when you break it up  [Applause]  [Music]  you said you wanted to far  to oblivion  [Music]  foreign  [Music]  wow